upfront group
Here we go...it's up-cami. This time with Risa Irie of Juice-Juice,
Risa Irie of Juice-Juice and Sumi Tashiro of Ocha-no-Awa.
This program will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the upfront group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
First of all, let's take a look behind the scenes at the two MCs.
I, Rie, am in the rehearsal period for our fall tour, which will have already started by the time this video is shown,
We are in the rehearsal period right now,
New member Mifchan Kawashima has joined us this time,
There are so many people to learn,
I saw Mifu-chan getting excited, and I told her that she would be fine,
I would watch the videos and learn new songs, but there were times when I still wasn't sure if I was doing it right or not.
In such cases, I was in the same audition class as Mifumi, so we are usually close to each other as seniors,
I am usually with Mifumi as a senior member who is quite close to her,
I help her out a little with dance and we work hard together in rehearsals.
It's wonderful.
I am with Mifusan Kawashima,
Mifusan.
With Mifusan Kawashima,
We had worked together as back-up dancers for Lalala's PVP and for Lalala's PVP at the 25th anniversary concert,
We practiced a lot together at that time,
We had practiced a lot together at that time, so we were both working very hard,
I was impressed by how hard she worked and how wonderful she was.
I was impressed by her ability to absorb things,
I thought it was really wonderful.
I, Tange, was a back-up dancer for Sayumi Michishige's "La La La La" PVP at the 25th anniversary live,
It was so cute.
I was very nervous,
It was my first experience as a back-up dancer.
It was very stimulating, and I learned a lot about facial expressions, dancing, and how to present myself,So it was very stimulating and I learned a lot about facial expressions, dance, and how to present myself,
It was a big thing for me,
I had the opportunity to work with Sayumi Michishige in Halo! I had worked with Sayumi Michishige before in the "1 plus 1" project of "Halo!
I was very happy to be able to perform with Sayumi Michishige again since then.
She was so cute.
Thank you very much.
We two MCs have a lot in common,
First of all, we are the same age,
Also, our member color is light purple.
Also, we joined Hello!
Also, we happen to be wearing new clothes today.
We will be presenting you with a lot of energy today, so please enjoy the show until the end.
So, let's start with this time's up-kami, here.
Tsubaki Factory - If you're only delusional, you're free to be free. Making of the music video shooting.
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single released on September 27,
Please take a look at the making of the music video for the song "Mousou Dake Dake Freedom", released on September 27th.
Best regards.
It looks like there's only one dance shot for one person.
We don't have a dance shot of all of us.
Do your best in one person's place.
I want to do my best to dance prettily and coolly, and
I think there will be a lot of image scenes.
I'm going to have lip syncs and image scenes.
So I'll do my best to make facial expressions that match the image.
I'll do my best!
Stopping at one step and going to bed
Let's go over his words.
Tell me what's wrong with him.
No, I don't want to know
Ah Ah Ah AhAh Ah Ah Ah
It's always like this.
I know, I know, I know.
I know, I know, I know
Ready action!
Cut!
Camera crew, on camera!
Okay, let's go!
Action!
One, two, one, two!
You guys having fun?
You want to have some fun?
One, two, one, two!
Yes, cut!
Okay, different action?
Okay, here we go!
Ready!
Cute.
So cute! Let's do more!
Smile!
Here we go! Ready!
Cut it!
Cut! Cut!
What do you like?
A monkey, maybe an elephant.
Something easy to understand.Easy to understand?
Easy to understand?
Goat?
This one's also in Cana.
I'll do a gorilla.
I'll do a monkey.
I'll do the monkey.
I don't think you should have a camera.
I'll do a monkey.
I'll do an action monkey.
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
I'll do it.
Ape.
You're a monkey.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go
You're not going, are you?
It's a robot!
Come on, robot!
Ready!
Action!
# Sink, sink, sink in front of everybody #
Good, good, good!
Like, everything's locked in place and only the arms move.
Only the neck moves.
It's so robotic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, this one can be an animal or a robot.
There are a few robots here.
They are pretending to be a robot.
Then let's do this one.Then let's do this.
Action.
Marie Manabee.
You okay?
Let's bounce.
Do you have feelings for this?
Goat! Goat!
Good morning!
All right! Let's go!
Everybody, pose for bling!
Pose, pose, pose, pose.
That's good.
That's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, let's start with the first one.
Okay.
All right, now we're gonna do a little bit of movement.
Here we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Here we go!
Snow flurries
Snowflakes are flurries
Snow flurries, snow flurries, snow flurries.
Cut!
Yes, cut!
Here we go! Ready, action!Here we go! Ready, action!
You can slowly turn the tables with your feet.
Action.
Wait a minute.
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly.
Cute.
Here we go, ladies.
Action.
Looking good, looking good.
Slowly. Slowly. On your feet.
Action!
Slower! Slower!
Slow down! Slowly moving forward!
Followed by Ji-mi-dai-a-de
to play
New
sea bass
Next to fly away
A life of rebirth
A life without dreams
Good bye
Love Love Love with an older lover
Farewell to delusions of being free
You'll keep me alive, once we get started
Move me, move me, move me, move me, move me
I was the king of the fight.
Let's go, coward. Step off.
You don't trust anyone.
The king of high stakes.
Well, this time I'm wearing three outfits... one for gals, one for uniforms, and one for princesses.This time I'm wearing three dresses, one for a gal, one for a school uniform, and one for a princess, so I'm wearing the princess dress.
I've never worn a dress like this before.
By the way, I'm wearing a light purple dress, which is a member's color.
By the way, I'm wearing a light purple dress, which is the color of the members.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how the music video will turn out.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how the music video will turn out, so I hope you'll pay attention to the costumes as well.
Let's get to the end
I have to dream
Good night
Bigger lip
Yes, OK.
Yes, coming up.
Yes, three curves.
Yes, hand claw.
Buttocks closed.
Shoulder clamps.
Here we go.
All right, let's move on.
Let's go!
Good job shooting the music video!
Let's go, ta-da!
Good job!
I just finished shooting the music video for "If You're Just Delusional, You're Free"!
I dyed my hair for the first time in my life.
I've shot many cool music videos, but this is really the first and last time I've dyed my hair brown.
But this is really the first and last time I've dyed my hair brown.
I think this is the first music video where you can see Riko Yamagishi with brown hair.
Yes, it's such a special music video!
This song has a surreal and mysterious worldview.
The repetition of the song makes you want to watch it over and over again.The kind of repetition that makes you want to watch it over and over again.
I'm sure you'll see a lot of "what was that expression? I'm sure there will be a lot of "what was that?
I hope you will pay attention to the details.
This was the last music video shoot for me as Riko Yamagishi.
I've shot many music videos since I was an indie singer, and I've been surrounded by really warm staff members.
I've been surrounded by really warm staff members, and I've really looked forward to every music video shoot.
I've really looked forward to every music video shoot.
They shoot beautifully and prettily every time, and the hair and makeup are different every time, and the outfits are different every time.
I was able to shoot a lot of pieces that allowed me to be many different people.
It was a place where I could show many new aspects of myself.
But this last one, the one for Freedom, where I'm not just delusional, was also a lot of fun.
I hope it will be like this. I hope you'll pay attention to me until the very end.
I hope you will pay attention to me until the very end.
And last but not least, the members gave me a surprise to congratulate me for all my hard work.
They presented me with a cake.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to enjoy it with everyone later.
I really appreciate all of you!
Thank you very much!
Please look at it a lot!
Yes, I've seen the images of Freedom's music video shoot, if only in my imagination,
I've seen a lot of solo dances of the members on TikTok,
I saw that the choreography was very catchy and the tune was very catchy,
It was really addictive,
At the 25th anniversary concert, I was watching from the side of the stage,
I was watching the 25th anniversary live from the side of the stage, and I was so impressed that the members could dance to the song,
I think they understood what I wanted to express in this song,
We were also pursuing surrealism in the filming,
I thought it was very nice that they changed their outfits a lot.
When I saw the music video, I saw a lot of costumes, and they changed into various outfits, and each outfit was very cute.I saw the music video, and there were many outfits, and they were changing into various outfits, and each outfit was very cute.
And then, when they were filming, there were scenes where they were walking around, and they were trying to make the speed a little faster, a little slower, etc. I was amazed at how particular they were about even that one movement,
I was amazed at how much care they put into even just that one movement.
This is the making of Tsubaki Factory's "Delusional Loud Freedom" music video.
I don't care if it's someone else's you, just fool me perfectly.
Tsubaki Factory But I don't mind. September 27 onsail.
It's still hot, so don't forget to stay hydrated.
Here's the next one. It's the vocal recording for Tea Horse's latest single.
Here are the vocal recordings of Ochanoma Mahoro mai Koinoba, Showa mo 2025 mo Wachawacha, and Ikumi Nishizaki from Ochanoma's newest single.
I'll do the A melody...I think I'll use 2021 for A.
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Instagram & Twitter Hodori
Comment Comment Comment
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이 Soundu Hodori
Instagram & Twitter Hodori
🐯 Sound Hodori 호돌이 Soundu Hodori
Yes, thank you very much.
Just one layer, just make it, three households surrounded by a chav table.
I saw the same show on TV.
I want to spread out and do things in different ways.
But it's much more tightly connected than in the old days.
It's Lion.
And then...And then...
B?
B.
How do you say it here?
I'll do it after the lever.
Okay. - Okay.
Why don't you...
Just leave it here.
It's just the living room.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to be relieved... but I want to leave first.
Let's go for a little more of that.
I want to be relieved.
Okay.
You want to be relieved.
Okay, I can do it. I can do it.
The pitch was almost right.
Yes, sir.
Just wait a minute.
It's the same.
No change.
No change, no change, no change.
Where can I be myself?
Not just in the living room.
The living room isn't high enough.
Not in the living room.
How did I do that?
That's it. That's it.
But it's a much more intimate live experience than it used to be.
I want to relax. I want to be relaxed.I want to be relieved I want to be relieved I want to be relieved I want to be relieved I want to be relieved
The inferiority complex of human beings never changes.
Where can I be myself?
Not just in the living room.
Oh, thank God, I'm whole.
Yay!
Sing the chorus, for now, to that magic horse.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes...
Well, Saccha's attack is good, so Waccha, too, that much perkier!
Wachcha! Yes, wattage, wattage, wattage!
Yay, magic horse!
Oh, great!
Okay, all right!
Waccha to Ikoi no Balmu no Yuku!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Wachcha wachcha wachcha wachcha wachcha tea place, sachcha sachcha sachcha tea place, sachcha sachcha sachcha tea place.
Okay, so that's taken care of, and then we're ready to go.
Then that's taken care of, and now we can go online, offline, family, friends, regulars...
I gotta sing "Family, Friends, Regulars." Regulars.
A place for tea, tea, tea, tea, tea, tea, tea, tea, tea, tea, a place for magic.
Online, offline, family, friends, regulars
Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Online, offline, right?
Kanoa, Attack is the best, yes.
Online Offline, you're the best at attacking, so, yes
Sing the lyrics
OK, here we go
Say, "Oh, no.
Oh, no, just like thatOh, no. No, no, no, no.
Just say yes, yes, yes.
I've only seen you in places like that.
I've only seen him say "wow" a few times.
What do you mean, "wow"?
Wow!
Chacha-chacha-chacha-chacha... tea room...
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go...
Nice and comfortable
It's the best
I'll only meet you in such a place
I'm sure it will never be born
Wacha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha
Kiyoshi Nishiki always looks so happy
This song is so cool and mature
With a mature smile
It's like he's singing with a mature smile on his face.
Then, I'll never be born, so I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I'll only meet you in a place like that.
I'm sure it won't happen.
Tea Room
Yes, that's good.
Okay, bye.
Yay!
End of section 3
Thank you very much
Yes, this song is...
It's very up-tempo.
It's very up-tempo, and it's about fun.It's full of fun and coolness.
and coolness.
Miku Nishizaki is a great singer.
is a very good singer.
So
Compared to when I recorded the song
I was so much better than when I recorded the song.
She sang the parts that I struggled with
I struggled with.
It's amazing.
That's what I thought of Miku Nishizaki.
Miku has her own way of singing.
I'm really impressed that you were able to do it from the beginning of the recording.
I think it's really amazing.
That's right.
When I saw the music video for this song
I saw the music video of this song, and I thought the latter half of the song was fast.
Like a two-part or four-part song.
I thought it was really interesting that it was composed in such a way
I thought it was very interesting.
The costumes are two poses.
Two poses
and so on.
It's very pop.
The music is cool, but it's also kind of funny.
but it's also got a little bit of fun to it.
I thought it was really nice.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Ochanoma.
Ochanoma MahorobaikoinovaOchanoma Mahorobaikoinoba
Showa and 2025 Mocha Mocha Mocha Mocha
It was a vocal recording by Miku Nishizaki
Cheer up!
Risa Irie of Juice-Juice and
and Sumine Tashiro of Ocha no Ame.
Next up is here!
Angulum Ai no Kedamono Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single
Please take a look at the vocal recording of Ayano Kawamura of Ai no Keidamono!
Okay, let's go ahead and record.
Yes, please do.
Okay, I'll start with the A melody.
I like the venom, and that's not the extent of it.
Four chords, let's go.
Um, you know, now, there's "love is not that much.
That was a great feeling. On the contrary, in the end, it's not about intuition. I think I was a little too persistent.
I thought it could have been lighter.
And overall, this song is a song about a carnal girl, so I thought it would be better if it was a little lighter.
It's not a smirk, but it's not a smirk, it's not a cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle, but it's like she's always aiming at you.
It's not a smirk, but it's like she's always aiming at you. It's like that.
Like, "I got this, I got this, I got this. I thought it would be nice if I could sing like that all the time.
So, I'm always kind of smiling, like a smile with a hint of a hint of a hint of a hint.
It would be nice if I could sing like that all the time.
Okay, I understand.
Let's go.
People ask me where I like it, but in the end, it's not the top volume.
It's not the kind of love that makes you withdraw after three days and three nights of worrying about it.
OK.
Okay, let's go to that part.Okay, let's do the part about that time.
We are girl" will be done later.
We'll start with the rest of the live performance for love, and go on to "I don't hold back".
The kind of love that makes you back down... that's not the extent of it.
Live for love. You're risking your life for love.
I won't hide it anymore, you're the target
That's a beautiful way to live, and I'm not holding back.
I've already got the right feeling.
But it's not like a gwaaaaahhhhhh, aggressive gwaaaahhhh...
It's like I'm playing with it.
It's a little bit like it's running forward rhythmically.
I'm a little concerned about this part, but OK, let's try it.
That's not the kind of love that makes you back down.
Live for love. You're risking your life for love.
I'm not gonna hide it anymore, you're the target.
I'm sure it's a beautiful way to live, and I'm not holding back.
I can't be shy with such a fragile creature.
I'll do the second line later, so just the first and third lines are fine.
Okay, let's try it.
It must be beautiful, I can't be shy
With a frail creature
Jump out now
Yes, yes, yes, the part with the frail creature, the frail feeling, that's OK, so you can laugh out loud at the "jump out of the way now" part.
I think it would be good if you do those two things well. Let's try one more time.
Let's jump out now.
Yes, OK, now let's go rustle.
Then let's go in a row.
Beloved, we are the mighty
Earth is a place where the law of the jungle prevails over the law of the jungle
Feel the breath of the air, and if the two of us are in syncFeel the breath. Feel the megapixels.
See, we're already hooked
We're in love, we're in love, we're in love
Our fiery encounters are on the verge of extinction
Lonely and delicate tokoroko
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
Feel how strong we really are
You suck at love. Prepare yourself.
Okay, well, uh, I'm almost done, so I'll fix it now.
Fourth string.
Look, it's already hooked.
Here, look, it's hooked.
See, it's already hooked. Pull it out and play it.
If you feel concern and your eyes meet, you can see I'm already in.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Now, the third string in the next block.
Let's see, you're a lonely, sensitive boy, huh?
And a lonely, sensitive boy, too.
Yes.
Let's see, the lonely part, you know, the lonely part, you have to get him out of it.
Yes, sir.
OK!
Okay.
Well, I guess that's all.
Okay, thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
This "Ai no Kedamono" at first gave me a strong image of dancing,
It was a very intense dance, like a dance practice version,
I was able to see more and more of it,
I saw more and more of it, and I had an image of how super cool it was,
I thought the song would be very difficult to sing because of the accents and the choked words,
I thought the song seemed to be very difficult to sing because of the accents and choked words, but I was impressed that Ms. Kawamura, who has an impression of being very cute, sang it so coolly.
I thought this song was really powerful, and the dance was also very powerful,
The director was very particular about the nuances of the song and conveyed them to the audience through their faces,
The director was very particular about the nuances, and I realized once again that nuances are very important.
This is Ayano Kawamura's vocal recording of Angulum's "Ai no Kedamono".
Tea lady! New Single
Tea Auntie! Mahalo ba! Ikaenoba!
Showa and 2021 Wachamacha!
Now on sale!
Long time no see! Thanks for watching!
It's time to say goodbye to Irielisa and Sumire Tashiro!
We've seen a lot of videos this time, but I, Tashiro, was really impressed with Aino Kawamura's recording of "Beast of Love".
I was impressed by Aino Kawamura's recording of "Beast of Love," and I thought it was a great reference for me.
I learned a lot from Aino Kawamura's singing voice and the way she added nuances.
I was able to learn a lot from them.
I, Rie, was very impressed with Tsubaki Factory's "If it's just fantasy, it's freedom!
I am a member of Tsubaki Factory's "Freedom if you're just delusional! I, Rie, really enjoyed the making of the music video for
I was really impressed by the making of the music video shooting
I was really impressed by the making of the music video for "Mousou dake wa Freedom!
I was so impressed by the way they wore so many costumes in one day
I've never experienced it so much myself
It was something I had never experienced
so I was really impressed by it.
I thought it was really amazing.I thought it was really great.
It's really great.
I really want to watch the music video again after seeing this video and find out how much I enjoyed it.
UpGod will be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT Group.
This time, our UpGod partner is the equivalent of a juice chew with a tea bean in it.
This time, we'll be chatting with Tashiro Sumide of Tea Noodles, bye-bye!
Next time on UpGod, we'll be showing you the recording of Tsubaki Factory's latest single, "Yuuki Itsu My Life".
and recording of Juice Juice Funky Flash!
Invite someone!